<resources>
    <string name="app_name">What Movie</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="title_tv_show">TV Show</string>
    <string name="title_card_movie">Movie Title</string>
    <string name="title_card_tv">TV Show Title</string>
    <string name="background_image">Background Image</string>
    <string name="image_poster">Image Poster</string>
    <string name="release_year">Release Year</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language</string>


    <!--Movies Title-->
    <array name="movies_title">
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Deadpool</item>
        <item>How To Train Your Dragon</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Mary Poppins Returns</item>
        <item>Preman Pensiun</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>Spiderman</item>
        <item>Venom</item>
    </array>

    <!--TV Show Title-->
    <array name="tv_title">
        <item>Arrow</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Fairy Tail</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>Flash</item>
        <item>Greys Anatomy</item>
        <item>Hanna</item>
        <item>Iron Fist</item>
        <item>Naruto Shippuden</item>
        <item>Supergirl</item>
        <item>The Simpson</item>
        <item>The Umbrella</item>
    </array>

    <!--Movies Realease Year-->
    <array name="movies_release_year">
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2019)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2019)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
        <item>(2018)</item>
    </array>

    <!--TV Realease Year -->
    <array name="tv_release_year">
        <item>(2012)</item>
        <item>(1986)</item>
        <item>(2009)</item>
        <item>(1999)</item>
        <item>(2014)</item>
        <item>(2005)</item>
        <item>(2019)</item>
        <item>(2017)</item>
        <item>(2007)</item>
        <item>(2015)</item>
        <item>(1989)</item>
        <item>(2019)</item>
    </array>

    <!--Movies Description-->
    <array name="movies_description">
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater
            kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a very large army, Orm plans to conquer
            the remaining ocean people and then to the surface of the world. What blocked his way
            was Arthur Curry, half-human half-human Orm half-brother and the true heir to the
            throne.
        </item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies continue to protect the world from threats that are
            too large to be handled by one hero, a new danger has arisen from the cosmic shadow:
            Thanos. An intergalactic despic despot, his aim is to gather all six Infinity Stones,
            artifacts of unimaginable strength, and use them to arouse his desires which are twisted
            in all reality. Everything that the Avengers have fought for has led to the present -
            the fate of the Earth and its very existence has never been more certain.
        </item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist
            John Deacon took the music world by storm when they formed the rock n roll band Queen in
            1970. Hit songs became an instant classic. When Mercurys increasingly wild lifestyle
            began to spiral out of control, Queen immediately faced her biggest challenge - finding
            ways to keep the band together amidst success and strength.
        </item>
        <item>On an escape in 1987, Bumblebee found a shelter in a junkyard in the small coastal
            town of California. Charlie, at the age of 18 and trying to find his place in the world,
            found Bumblebee, a battle scar and broken. When Charlie turned it on, he quickly learned
            that this wasnt an ordinary yellow VW bug.
        </item>
        <item>Kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to hold Deadpool PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a
            story of Putri Bride full of miracles, wonders and zero F.
        </item>
        <item>When Hiccup fulfilled his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothlesss
            discovery of an untested and difficult-to-capture pair pulled Night Fury away. When the
            danger increases at home and the Hiccup government as the village head is tested, both
            dragons and motorists must make the impossible decision to save their kind.
        </item>
        <item>Earth is peaceful after the Power Tournament. Realizing that the universe still has
            many stronger people to see, Goku spends all of his training days reaching greater
            heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta were confronted by a Saiyan named Broly whom they
            had never seen before. The Saiyan people should have been almost completely destroyed in
            the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so what was this person doing on Earth? The meeting
            between the three Saiyan who had followed this very different destiny turned into an
            extraordinary battle, with even Frieza (returning from Hell) trapped in the mix.
        </item>
        <item>In the London Depression, Jane and Michael Banks who had grown up, along with Michaels
            three children, were visited by enigmatic Mary Poppins after a personal loss. Through
            her unique magical skills, and with the help of her friend Jack, she helps families
            rediscover the joy and magic lost in their lives.
        </item>
        <item>After three years, the Muslihat (Epi Kusnandar) business, which had retired as a thug,
            had a problem. Decline in sales. Muslihat also faced a new problem when Safira (Safira
            Maharani), her only daughter, grew up in adolescence and began to be visited by boys. A
            bigger problem: friction between his former subordinates.
        </item>
        <item>A hard war fighter and his Moorish commander waged a brave uprising against the
            corrupt British crown.
        </item>
        <item>Miles Morales juggled his life between being a middle school student and being a
            spider man. When Wilson Kingpin Fisk uses a super collider, the others from across
            Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.
        </item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock tried to return after the scandal, but
            inadvertently hosted Venom, a powerful and powerful alien symbiot. Immediately, he must
            rely on his new powers to protect the world from shadow organizations that seek their
            own symbiosis.
        </item>
    </array>

    <!--TV Description-->
    <array name="tv_description">
        <item>Spoiled billionaire playboy Oliver Queen is missing and presumed dead when his yacht
            is lost at sea. He returns five years later a changed man, determined to clean up the
            city as a hooded vigilante armed with a bow.
        </item>
        <item>Long ago in the mountains, a fighting master known as Gohan discovered a strange boy
            whom he named Goku. Gohan raised him and trained Goku in martial arts until he died. The
            young and very strong boy was on his own, but easily managed. Then one day, Goku met a
            teenage girl named Bulma, whose search for the mystical Dragon Balls brought her to Goku
            home. Together, they set off to find all seven and to grant her wish.
        </item>
        <item>Lucy is a 17-year-old girl, who wants to be a full-fledged mage. One day when visiting
            Harujion Town, she meets Natsu, a young man who gets sick easily by any type of
            transportation. But Natsu isnt just any ordinary kid, hes a member of one of the worlds
            most infamous mage guilds: Fairy Tail.
        </item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin Sweet animated series featuring the
            adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois
            have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and
            taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and
            Chris (the middle kid, hes not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final
            member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie
            in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
        </item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is
            struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of
            super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen
            guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to
            discover he is not the only meta-human who was created in the wake of the accelerator
            explosion -- and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with
            S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close
            friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it wont
            be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become...The Flash.
        </item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle’s Grey
            Sloan Memorial Hospital.
        </item>
        <item>This thriller and coming-of-age drama follows the journey of an extraordinary young
            girl as she evades the relentless pursuit of an off-book CIA agent and tries to unearth
            the truth behind who she is. Based on the 2011 Joe Wright film.
        </item>
        <item>Danny Rand resurfaces 15 years after being presumed dead. Now, with the power of the
            Iron Fist, he seeks to reclaim his past and fulfill his destiny.
        </item>
        <item>Naruto Shippuuden is the continuation of the original animated TV series Naruto.The
            story revolves around an older and slightly more matured Uzumaki Naruto and his quest to
            save his friend Uchiha Sasuke from the grips of the snake-like Shinobi, Orochimaru.
            After 2 and a half years Naruto finally returns to his village of Konoha, and sets about
            putting his ambitions to work, though it will not be easy, as He has amassed a few (more
            dangerous) enemies, in the likes of the shinobi organization; Akatsuki.
        </item>
        <item>Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was
            13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously
            hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her powers, until she has to
            reveal them during an unexpected disaster, setting her on her journey of heroism.
        </item>
        <item>Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and
            everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well
            as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture
            icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for
            itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.
        </item>
        <item>A dysfunctional family of superheroes comes together to solve the mystery of their
            fathers death, the threat of the apocalypse and more.
        </item>
    </array>

    <!--Movies Poster-->
    <array name="movies_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_preman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>
    </array>

    <!--TV Poster-->
    <array name="tv_poster">
        <item>@drawable/poster_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_family_guy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_grey_anatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_iron_fist</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_naruto_shipudden</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_simpson</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_the_umbrella</item>
    </array>

    <!--Movies Background-->
    <array name="movies_background">
        <item>@drawable/background_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_marypoppins</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_preman</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/background_venom</item>
    </array>

    <!--TV Background-->
    <array name="tv_background">
        <item>@drawable/tv_arrow</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_dragon_ball</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_fairytail</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_familyguy</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_flash</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_grey</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_hanna</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_iron</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_naruto</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_supergirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_thesimpson</item>
        <item>@drawable/tv_theumbrella</item>
    </array>
</resources>
